LEOPOLD ROSE

72006 Pole Street, Ferndale, MI 48220 jpserra09@emailme.com (248.1-901-2345

Solutions-focused and goal-oriented software engineer with eight years of experience in implementing advanced technology and business solutions in public and private industries. Demonstrates strong analytical and problem-solving skills and the ability to follow through with projects from inception to completion,

EDUCATION

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION SYSTEMS

Michigan Central University Detroit, MI September 2019 - Present

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE **IN** COMPUTER SCIENCE

Michigan Central University Mount Pleasant, MI September 2008 -July 2012

KEY SKILLS

- · Proactive team player
- Application development using
 C#, .NET, PHP, HTML, Java,
 MySQL, SQL, PostgreSQL, Turbo
 C, Visual Basic, Perl + Template
 Toolkit and LAMPP/XAMPP
- Project management using dotProject
- Microsoft Office and OpenOffice tools
- RedHaf, Mandrake, SuSe, and Linux operating systems

CERTIFICATIONS

- Microsoft Certified Solutions
 Developer, 2014
- AWS Certified Solutions Architect
 Professional, 2017
- Oracle Certified Developer
 MySQL 5.6 Developer, 2018

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Accenture Digital Delivery Center, Detroit, MI August 2018 - Present

- Development, support, and maintenance of 36 clients' web reservations systems
- Handle the customization of clients' systems, including functional requirements documentation, use cases, actual coding, unit testing, and deployment
- Development, support, and maintenance of web services APIs
- Scheduling and delegating of work items to a team of 20 members

IT SPECIALIST I

Department of Technology, Management and Budget, Lansing, MI October 2012 -July 2018

- Administered DTMB's personnel information system, which covers various online administration services such as Personnel Daily Time Report Management, External Business Activity Monitoring and Approval, Room and Facility Reservation and Personnel Performance Feedback Management and Monitoring
- Managed and monitored the implementation of the front-end and back-end development of the Testing, Analysis and Calibration Automation project, which involved 15 team members
- Led the design and implementation of Michigan's network infrastructure upgrades, which comprised four main servers and 21 backup servers located across the state
- Configured servers using Fedora core 5, installed PHP and mySQL in a ch root environment, installed and configured Symfony, managed project subversions and performed daily database backup